-It was a nice retirement party. -I guess.
- Joli départ àla retraite. - Sûrement.
Still, it's a shame Professor Rothman was forced to step down.
Dommage que le professeur Rothman doive nous quitter.
Well, what choice did the university have? He snapped.
L'université n'avait pas le choix. Il a craqué.
It happens to theoretical physicists all the time.
Ça arrive à tous les physiciens.
I wonder how long Sheldon's got.
Combien de temps tiendra Sheldon ?
These shrimp are all the same size.
Ces crevettes ont toutes la même taille.
There's no logical order to eat them in.
Il n'y a aucun ordre logique.
Can't be very long.
Ça ne devrait pas tarder.
Hey, look, there's Rothman's empty office.
Regardez. C‘est l'ancien bureau de Rothman.
-Sad. -Yeah.
- C‘est triste. - Oui.
-lndeed. -So sad.
- En effet. - Tellement triste.
Dibs.
Prems.
What's up, fellas?
Salut, les gars.
What are you doing here, Kripke?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais la, Kripke ?
Measuring my new office for drapes.
Je prends les mesures de mon nouveau bureau.
This is not your office. It hasn't been assigned yet.
Ce n‘est pas le tien. Il n‘a pas encore été attribué.
I called dibs at Christmas when Rothman tried to have intercourse...
J'ai dit prems à Noël lorsque Rothman essayait
Dibs? I mean, this is a university, not a playground.
Prems ? C‘est une université, pas une cour de récréation.
Offices are not assigned because someone called dibs.
Les bureaux ne sont pas attribués à celui qui dit prems.
-You just called dibs. -Shut it.
- Tu Viens juste de le faire. - Tais-toi.
Offices are assigned by seniority. I arrived at the university first.
Mais par ancienneté.
I arrived at the office first. I'm the proverbial early bird.
Etj‘étais le premier arrivé dans ce bureau.
-Gentlemen. -Mr. Rothman.
- Messieurs. - M. Rothman.
-Professor Rothman.
- Professeur Rothman.
Good evening.
Bonne soirée.
LEONARD: Good evening. -See you.
- Bonsoir. - Au revoir.
I'm glad that men are wearing hats again.
Génial, les chapeaux reviennent a la mode.
They're so distinguished.
C‘est si distingué.
-I got you a little something. -A little something?
- J'ai un petit cadeau pour toi. - Ah bon ?
Oh, it--
ou, je...
What? This is huge.
Mais c‘est énorme.
What's huge is what you've done for me.
Comme ce que tu fais pour moi.
Oh, no, Amy, I haven't done anything.
Non, Amy. Je n'ai rien fait.
No, no. Before I met you, I was a mousy wallflower.
Avant de te rencontrer, je faisais tapisserie.
But look at me now.
Mais regarde—moi maintenant.
...with a posse, a boyfriend...
avec des copains, un petit ami
...and a new lace bra that hooks in the front, of all things.
et un nouveau soutien—gorge qui s‘attache devant.
-Open it, open it. -Okay.
- Ouvre—le. - D‘accord.
I wanted to get you something you didn't have.
Je voulais t'offrir un cadeau unique.
-Do you like it? -Do I like it? Wow.
- Tu l'aimes ? - Si je l'aime ?
So where you gonna hang it?
Où vas-tu le mettre ?
Oh, my Go-- Hang it. Wow. Um....
Mon Dieu, où vais-je le mettre ?
You know, I'd have to get a hook and nails and a hammer, and--
Il va me falloir un marteau, des clous...
-No problem. -Oh, look.
- Pas de problème. - Ah.
You've got-- You just-- You got it all right there. Wow.
Tu as vraiment tout prévu.
I found him. He's in the bathroom.
Je l'ai trouvé. Il est dans les toilettes.
-President Seibert? -Can't this wait?
- Président ? - Ça ne peut pas attendre ?
I'm sorry, we just need a word.
Désolé mais il faut qu'on parle.
Now? You realize I'm your boss and lam holding my penis.
Maintenant ? Je suis votre chef etje tiens mon pénis.
Sheldon, give the man some privacy.
Sheldon, laisse—lui de l‘intimité.
I'm sorry, this guy's got no respect for boundaries.
Ce type ne connait pas les limites.
What do you want?
Que voulez-vous ?
Will you tell this lunatic that Rothman's office is mine?
Que vous lui disiez que le bureau de Rothman est a moi.
Take this up with your department chairman.
Voyez-ça avec le responsable de votre département.
His assistant said he was on sabbatical.
Son assistant nous a dit qu'il était absent.
Although, we distinctly heard his office window open and shut.
Mais nous avons clairement entendu sa fenêtre s‘ouvrir.
Gentlemen, there's a task I'm trying to accomplish here...
Il y a une tâche que j'aimerais accomplir
-...and I'm having trouble doing it. -Oh, my.
- mais je n‘y arrive pas. - Vraiment ?
President Seibert, I don't mean to be an alarmist...
Je ne veux pas être alarmiste
...but difficulty initiating a urine stream...
mais une difficulté a uriner
...could be a symptom of benign prostatic hyperplasia.
peut être un syndrome d‘hyperplasie de la prostate.
If you're interested, I can send you a link to a YouTube video...
Je peux vous envoyer le lien d‘une Vidéo YouTube
...that'll show you how to perform your own rectal exam.
qui vous montre comment pratiquer un examen rectal.
Yeah, helpful hint: trim your nails first.
Petit conseil : coupez-vous les ongles d'abord.
Ignore him, President Seibert.
lgnorez-le.
I'm sure a young man such as yourself has a perfectly healthy prostate.
Un homme aussi jeune que vous a une prostate en parfait état.
Oh, he's just trying to butter you up.
Il essaie de vous graisser la patte.
And for the record, butter is an excellent lubricant for your rectal exam.
D‘ailleurs, la graisse est un excellent lubrifiant pour l‘examen.
Gentlemen, I'm going to allow you to work this out...
Je vais vous autoriser à régler ce souci entre vous
...because, A, you're brilliant scientists...
car vous êtes de brillants scientifiques
...and, B, as far as who gets Rothman's office...
et que je me fous royalement de quel idiot aura ce bureau.
Well, as long as we're here, I might as well take a leak.
Tant qu'on est la, je vais me soulager aussi.
You're in my spot.
C‘est mon urinoir.
That is big.
C‘est énorme.
So big.
Tellement énorme.
-And ugly. -So ugly.
- Et affreux. - Tellement affreux.
What am I gonna do?
Qu'est-ce que je vais faire ?
I don't know. You can't take it down. You'll break her heart.
Tu ne peux pas l'enlever. Ca lui ferait du mal.
Look at that face.
Regarde ce Visage.
That enormous, unsettling, crazy face.
Ce visage énorme, dérangeant et pervers.
Any chance I'll learn to love it?
Je vais m‘y faire, non ?
That depends, do you like pictures of yourself where you look like a man?
Ça dépend. Tu aimes te voir en homme ?
-All right. It's gotta go. -What will you tell Amy?
- Il faut que je l'enlève. - Que vas-tu lui dire ?
How about I tell her the painting makes you feel jealous because you're not in it?
Que tu es jalouse car tu n'es pas dessus ?
Oh, nuh-uh. What if she gets me one?
Non. Aprés, elle m'en offrira un.
I already have a picture of me and Howard's mom...
J'ai déjà la photo de moi et de ma belle-mère
...getting our hair cornrowed in Venice Beach. I've suffered enough.
en train de nous faire faire des tresses. C‘est assez.
I could take it down and put it up when she comes over, but it's kind of heavy.
Je pourrais l‘enlever et le remettre quand elle Vient mais il est lourd.
Too bad you're not as strong as the dude in the painting.
Dommage que tu n'aies pas la force de ton alter ego masculin.
Would you look at this?
Regardez—ça.
I paid $25 to some kid on eBay for a handcrafted Harry Potter wand.
J'ai offert 25 $ à un gosse sur eBay pour la baguette d‘Harry Potter.
He sent me a stick.
Il m‘a envoyé un bâton.
He went into his backyard, he picked up a stick.
Il est allé dans son jardin chercher un bâton.
It's numbered. Heh.
Il y a un numéro.
Ooh. Limited edition. Nice.
Une édition limitée. Génial.
-Oh, that'll be Kripke. -What's he doing here?
- Ça doit être Kripke. - Ici ?
We're going to work this office situation out like gentlemen.
Nous allons résoudre ce problème comme des hommes.
And if that doesn't work, I'm going to poison his tea.
Sinon,je mettrai du poison dans son thé.
-Cooper. -Kripke. Come in.
- Cooper. - Kripke. Entré.
I'm making tea. Would you like a cup?
J‘ai fait du thé. Ça te dit ?
Am I wearing a summer frock? No, I don't want tea.
J'ai l‘air d‘aimer le thé ? Non, merci.
Let's get down to brass tacks.
Venons-en aux faits.
Fine. In the interest of preserving our friendship--
Dans l‘intérêt de préserver notre amitié…
-We're not friends. -Well...
- Quelle amitié ? - Bien,
...that's a little hard to hear, but all right.
c‘est dur a entendre mais c‘est vrai.
As you know, the essence of diplomacy is compromise.
L‘essence de la diplomatie étant le compromis,
With that in mind, I propose the following.
je te propose ce qui suit:
I will take Rothman's office...
je prends le bureau de Rothman
...and you will find a way to be okay with that.
et tu devras t'en accommoder.
How about I take Rothman's office and you go suck a lemon?
Et si je prenais le bureau
You sure I can't get you that cup of tea?
Tu ne veux vraiment pas de thé ?
How about you decide this with Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock?
Si vous jouiez a Pierre—Papier- Ciseaux-Lézard-Spock ?
Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock...
Pierre-Papier-Ciseaux-Lézard-Spock
...was created by Internet pioneer Sam Kass...
a été créé par le pionnier d'Internet
...as an improvement on the game Rock, Paper, Scissors.
comme une extension du jeu Pierre-Papier-Ciseaux.
All hail Sam Kass.
Gloire à Sam Kass.
ALL: Hail.
Gloire atoi.
How does it work?
Et les régies ?
Oh, it's very simple.
C‘est simple.
Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock...
Les ciseaux coupent le papier qui recouvre la pierre.
...rock crushes lizard, lizard poisons Spock...
La pierre écrase le lézard qui empoisonne Spock.
...Spock smashes scissors, scissors decapitates lizard...
Spock casse les ciseaux qui décapitent le lézard.
...lizard eats paper, paper disproves Spock...
Le lézard mange le papier qui réfute Spock.
...Spock vaporizes rock...
Spock vaporise la pierre
...and, as it always has, rock crushes scissors.
qui finit toujours par écraser les ciseaux.
I'm sorry, can you repeat that?
Tu peux répéter ?
Well, of course. Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock...
Les ciseaux coupent le papier qui recouvre la pierre.
...rock crushes lizard, lizard poisons Spock...
La pierre écrase le lézard qui empoisonne Spock.
...Spock smashes scissors, scissors decapitates lizard...
Spock casse les ciseaux qui décapitent le lézard.
...lizard eats paper, paper disproves Spock...
Le lézard mange le papier qui réfute Spock.
...Spock vaporizes rock...
Spock vaporise la pierre
...and, as it always has, rock crushes scissors.
qui finit toujours par écraser les ciseaux.
Almost got it. One more time.
J‘y suis presque. Encore.
Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock--
Les ciseaux coupent le papier...
Sheldon, stop. He's screwing with you.
Sheldon, arrête. Il se moque de toi.
Is he?
Vraiment ?
Well, then, seems we have reached an impasse.
Alors, nous sommes dans une impasse.
I see no other option than to challenge you to a duel.
Je vais devoir te défier en duel.
I'd smack you with a glove, butjust last week, I packed away my winter things.
Je t'aurais bien giflé avec un gant
It's the 21st century, you can't have a duel.
On est au XXIe siècle. C‘est interdit.
Hang on, Howard.
Attends, Howard.
Barry, how good of a shot are you?
Barry, tu vises bien ?
Not pistols. Minds.
Pas avec des armes. Avec notre esprit.
A trivia contest. And you may choose the field of battle.
Un concours de culture générale. Tu choisis le théme :
Star Trek trivia, Star Trek: Next Generation trivia...
Star Trek, Star Trek : La Nouvelle Génération,
...Star Trek: Deep Space Nine trivia, Star Trek: Voyager trivia...
Star Trek : Deep Space Nine, Star Trek : Voyager
...or model trains.
ou les trains miniatures.
You have an advantage in trivia. You have an eidetic memory.
Tu as un avantage. Tu as une mémoire photographique.
Plus, I haven't watched Star Trek...
Etje n'ai pas regardé Star Trek
...since I discovered the strip club near my apartment has a free buffet.
depuis que j'ai découvert ce club de strip—tease avec buffet gratuit.
It's hard to find something you're both equally good at.
Il faut trouver un sujet où vous étes bons tous les deux.
Is there anything you're equally bad at?
Ou un où vous étes nuls ?
-Sports.
- Le sport.
All right, this is one-on-one, first to five wins the office.
C‘est un-contre-un. Le premier a cinq gagne.
Any questions? Yes, Sheldon.
Des questions ? Oui, Sheldon.
Five what?
Cinq quoi ?
Balls in the basket.
Ballons dans le panier.
That's out, right?
Elle sort, non ?
Time. Ran out of room.
Temps mort. Je suis sorti.
You know those terrible things bullies used to do to us?
Vous savez ce que les brutes nous infligeaient ?
-Yeah? -I get it.
- Oui. - Je les comprends maintenant.
-He did that on purpose. -No, he didn't.
- Il l‘a fait exprès. - Non.
Nothing that's happening here is being done on purpose.
Rien dans ce gymnase n‘est fait exprès.
Okay, forget one-on-one. Let's try a free-throw contest.
Oubliez le un-contre-un.
First person who makes a basket wins the office.
Le premier à marquer un panier a gagné.
-Making it too easy there, Hofstadter. -Nope. No, I'm not.
- C‘est trop facile. - On va voir.
Use the Force, Sheldon. Use the Force.
Utilise la Force, Sheldon. La Force.
I'm gonna need more Force.
Il me faut plus de Force.
All right, Cooper. Prepare to have your heart broken.
Prépare—toi a avoir le cœur brisé.
Do I get points for that?
Ça me fait combien de points ?
All right, we gave it 45 minutes.
Ça fait 45 minutes.
It's no longer funny. Let's try something else.
Ce n‘est plus drôle. Essayons autre chose.
What do you propose?
Comme quoi ?
Highest bounce wins the office.
Le plus haut rebond gagne.
Oh, you are going down, Cooper.
Tu vas perdre, Cooper.
I don't think so, Kripke.
Je ne crois pas.
I've bounced many a rubber ball in my day.
J‘étais un pro dela halle magique autrefois.
All right. That's enough trash talk.
On n‘a pas besoin de détails.
One, two, three.
Un, deux, trois.
Sheldon was higher.
Sheldon était le plus haut.
Congratulations, Sheldon, you win the office.
Félicitations. Tu as gagné le bureau.
Who's unsatisfactory in PE now?
Qui est nul en sport maintenant ?
Oh, what a great movie.
Quel super film!
I cannot believe you've never seen Grease.
Tu n‘avaisjamais vu Grease ?
My mother didn't allow me to watch it.
Ma mère me l‘a interdit.
She was afraid it might encourage me to join a gang.
Elle avait peur queje rejoigne un gang.
I gotta go. I gotta get up early.
J‘y vais. Je me lève tôt demain.
My company's testing a new steroid that doesn't shrink testicles...
On teste un stéroïde sans impact sur les testicules
...and the last one there has to do the measuring.
et le dernier arrivé doit les mesurer.
Guess I should get going too.
Je devrais y aller aussi.
Good night, painting Penny.
Bonne nuit, Penny peinte.
Good night, real Penny.
Bonne nuit, vraie Penny.
Good night, real Amy.
Bonne nuit, vraie Amy.
You don't have to say good night to painting Amy, she's never leaving.
Pas la peine de le dire à Amy peinte, elle ne part pas.
-Good night, real Penny. -Bye.
- Bonne nuit, vraie Penny. - Salut.
Good night, transvestite Penny.
Bonne nuit, Penny travestie.
Okay, let us take you off the wall.
Enlevons-ça du mur.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Loin des yeux, loin du cœur.
I wish.
Enfin, j‘espère.
Can I borrow that movie?
Je peux t‘emprunter le film ?
Those singing hooligans really got my motor running.
Ces loubards qui chantent me font vraiment de l'effet.
Sure, sure. Enjoy.
Bien sûr. Prends—le.
You get it back to me when you can or--
Tu me le ramèneras quand...
You keep it. It's just gonna be my gift to you.
Non, garde—le. C‘est un cadeau.
Thank you. Wait-- Where'd the painting go?
Merci. Où est le tableau ?
-lt's right over there. -Why?
- Juste la. - Pourquoi ?
l have no idea. That is weird.
Aucune idée. C‘est bizarre.
You hate it.
Tu le détestes.
-No, no, no. It's just-- It's a little big. -I feel like an idiot.
- Non. Il estjuste imposant. - Je me sens bête.
You're not an idiot. Just help me put it back up.
Mais non. Aide—moi ale remettre.
So you can just take it down when I leave?
Pour que tu le retires après ?
-I don't need your pity. -Oh, Amy, come on.
- Je n'ai pas besoin de ta pitié. - Attends.
I'm just glad I didn't go for the sculpture.
Heureusement que je n'ai pas choisi la statue.
I see why victors love them.
Je comprends les vainqueurs.
I'm happy for you, Sheldon, but I have to admit...
Je suis ravi pour toi mais je dois avouer
...l'm going to miss sharing an office with you.
que notre cohabitation va me manquer.
Oh, of course you are.
C‘est normal.
Well, feel free to drop by any time.
Passe quand tu veux.
-Thank you. -Yeah. Call first.
- Merci. - Mais appelle d'abord.
Oh, hello.
Bonjour.
Professor Rothman.
Professeur Rothman.
This isn't your office anymore. You're retired.
Ce n‘est plus votre bureau. Vous êtes retraité.
I think the word you're looking for is "invisible."
Je dirais plutôt "invisible".
I came to say I'm sorry.
Je Viens m'excuser.
-Don't bother. -Oh, Amy, please.
- Pas la peine. - S'il te plaît.
I'm so humiliated. I sat there the whole time we were watching Grease...
Je suis humiliée. Tout le long du film, je croyais
-...thinking you liked the painting. -I know.
- que tu aimais ce tableau. - Je sais.
l was a fool from "summer loving"...
Je suis passée pour une idiote dela premiére àla dernière chanson.
You're absolutely right.
Tu as raison.
I should have been honest and told you the gift was too much.
J'aurais dû être honnête et te dire que c‘était trop.
Yes, too much. Because our friendship is fundamentally asymmetrical.
Notre amitié est profondément asymétrique.
I clearly like you more than you like me.
Je t'aime plus que tu ne m'aimes.
I don't think you put a number on how much one person likes another.
On ne peut pas mettre un chiffre sur l'affection.
I bought you a painting that's 12 square feet in area.
Je t'ai acheté un tableau d‘1 m! de surface.
There's a number.
C‘est un chiffre.
Amy, come--
Amy...
If you don't like feet, you can try dollars. The painting set me back 3 grand.
On peut aussi parler d‘argent. Ça m‘a coûté 3 000 $.
Three gr--? Oh, my God.
Trois mille… Mon Dieu.
Look, Amy, all you need to know is you are my friend.
Tu dois juste savoir que tu es mon amie.
I don't wanna lose you out of my life.
Je ne veux pas te perdre.
I'm sorry, I'm just having trouble believing you right now.
J'ai du mal ate croire, maintenant.
-Grab your hammer. -No, damage is done.
- Prends ce marteau. - Le mal est fait.
Okay, look, I didn't wanna say this...
Je ne voulais rien dire
...but the real reason I took the painting down...
mais si j'ai enlevé le tableau, c‘est parce que
...was because it made Bernadette veryjealous.
Bernadette était très jalouse.
Oh, my goodness.
Bonté divine!
How could I have not seen that?
J'aurais dû y penser.
The painting is a constant reminder that of the three of us...
Ce tableau lui rappelle sans cesse
...she is the least cool.
qu'elle est la moins cool d‘entre nous.
Yeah, that's what it is, so....
C‘est tout a fait ça.
-You have such a good heart. -Oh. I try.
- Tu es si gentille. - J'essaie de l'être.
-Come on. -Well, where are we going?
- Viens. - Où on va ?
We're gonna put this back up.
Remettre le tableau chez toi.
What about Bernadette?
Et Bernadette ?
Oh, screw her. She's just lucky we let her hang out with us.
Elie ajuste dela chance de nous avoir.
What are you doing?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ?
I'm trying to raise the temperature in here...
J'essaie de réchauffer la pièce
...before my nipples tear through my shirt.
avant que mes tétons ne déchirent mon tee-shirt.
Why don't you just turn up the thermostat?
Pourquoi tu ne tournes pas le thermostat ?
Aha. Good question.
Bonne question.
It turns out that the thermostat for my new office isn't in my new office.
Le thermostat de mon bureau n‘est pas dans mon bureau.
No, it's next door in Professor Davenport's office...
Il est dans le bureau du professeur Davenport
...who is currently enjoying the hot flashes associated with menopause.
qui connaît actuellement les joies dela ménopause.
Why is there a hole here?
Et ce trou ?
Why is there a hole in my new office?
Pourquoi y a-t-il un trou ?
I've narrowed it down to two possibilities.
J'ai retenu deux possibilités.
There was something in the wall that someone outside the wall wanted.
Quelqu'un avait perdu quelque chose dans ce mur.
Or the more disturbing...
Ou plus étrange,
...there was something in the wall that wanted out.
quelque chose dans ce mur voulait en sortir.
At least you got a window that opens. That's nice.
Au moins, ta fenêtre s'ouvre. C‘est génial.
Oh. Is it? Listen.
Vraiment ? Ecoute.
-What, you don't like wind chimes? -No, I hate them, but it gets worse.
- Tu n‘aimes pas les carillons ? - Je les déteste. Attends.
-There it is. -The bird?
- La. - L'oiseau ?
Yeah, it's completely out of tune with the wind chimes.
Il n‘est pas en rythme avec les carillons.
-So? -You don't get it, do you?
- Et ? - Vous ne comprenez pas ?
That's a mockingbird. Mockingbirds can change their song...
C‘est un oiseau moqueur. Il peut changer de chant
...which means he's out of tune on purpose.
donc il fait exprès de mal chanter.
He's mocking me.
Il se moque de moi.
The growing realization that you are one wacky bastard? Yep.
Que tu es en train de perdre la téte ? Oui.
No. The vibration.
Non. La vibration.
We are directly underneath the geology lab...
Nous sommes sous le labo de géologie
...and they're running their sieve shakers again.
et ils utilisent leur tamis.
Hey, gravel monkeys, you need to shake rocks?
Vous avez besoin de secouer des pierres ?
Tryjiggling your heads around!
Essayez plutôt de secouer votre tête.
-Sheldon, relax. -How can I relax?
- Détends-toi. - Comment ?
My nervous system is being stretched out like the strings of a harp...
Mes nerfs sont tendus comme les cordes d‘une harpe
...and plucked by holes and birds and wind...
et pincés par des trous, des oiseaux, le vent
...and the low-hanging scrotum of the difficult-to-evict Professor Rothman.
et le scrotum tombant de l'inévitable professeur Rothman.
If you're not happy, just let Kripke have the office.
Laisse ce bureau a Kripke.
Wait, and let him win? Do I look crazy to you?
Et le laisser gagner ? J'ai l‘air d'un fou ?
We're trying to think down here, you geode-loving feldsparjockeys!
On essaie de réfléchir ici, géologues àla noix!
And you, the notes are C, D, E, G and A.
Quant a toi, les notes sont do, ré, mi, sol et la.
You pick one or I'm chopping down that tree!
Chante juste ou j‘abats cet arbre.
-How's that? -Little higher on the right.
- Et la ? - Plus haut sur la droite.
-Now? -Little more.
- Encore.
No. That's got it.
Non. C‘est parfait.
Yeah, okay. That's good.
Oui, c‘est bien.
-l'll let you in on a little secret. -Mm.
Je vais te dire un secret.
Originally, we were painted nude.
Ala base, nous étions nues.
But I had him add clothes because it was an unnecessary challenge...
Je lui ai dit de rajouter les habits.
Yeah, good call.
Bonne idée.
If you change your mind, all it would take is warm soapy water and a couple of sponges.
Si tu changes d‘avis, il suffit d'un peu d‘eau
-You're talking about the painting, right? -Sure.
- Tu parles bien du tableau ? - Bien sûr.
SHELDON: Help! Somebody, help!
A l'aide !
What happened?
Qu'est-ce qu'il y a ?
l was trying to see what was in here and my head got stuck.
Je voulais regarder dans le trou et ma tête s‘est coincée.
Why would you do that?
Pourquoi ?
SHELDON: It's called scientific curiosity.
Simple curiosité scientifique.
Now go get butter.
Va chercher du beurre.
Okay, okay. Hang in there. I'll be right back.
Attends-moi. Je reviens.
[English - us - an]
[French]